dudecomedy.com 2016-12-01

# Privacy Policy

### [Privacy Policy](http://dudecomedy.com/privacy-policy/)

Effective as of 06/14/2015.

MTD ENTERTAINMENT LLC (“DudeComedy”) is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to DudeComedy’s online and mobile website, services, and applications (“Site”), and has established this privacy statement (“Statement”) to inform you of DudeComedy’s information gathering and dissemination policies and practices regarding your use of the Site.

1\. SITE INFORMATION COLLECTION

Information Collected

As you navigate the Site, DudeComedy may collect information such as your Internet Protocol address, Web browser information, and your actions while on the Site. This information will be collected, if at all, through the use of commonly-used information-gathering tools, such as cookies and Web beacons. Standing alone, this information does not personally identify you. When expressing interest in DudeComedy’s products or services, you may have the option to provide contact information such as your name, organization name, address, e-mail address, phone number. Providing this optional information is voluntary on your part, and in the absence of providing such information you remain anonymous to DudeComedy. You may also have the option of engaging in other forms of communication such as online forums or communities, during which DudeComedy may collect a record of information disclosed by you. If you access the Site on your mobile telephone or other mobile device, DudeComedy also may collect your unique device identifier and mobile device IP address (e.g. MAC address), as well as information about your device’s operating system, mobile carrier, and mobile Internet browsers, your precise location information, and other information described in this Policy.

Use of Information Collected

DudeComedy and its affiliates and business partners may use non-personally identifiable information collected from you to operate and improve the Site, diagnose technical problems, to respond to your request for information, or to send you unsolicited communications about products, services, promotions, partners or events that may interest you. In no event will DudeComedy share personally-identifiable information, including credit card or other financially-sensitive information, without your consent except in response to legal process, for example in response to a court order or a subpoena, or in response to a law enforcement agency’s request. DudeComedy also may disclose such information to third parties in connection with fraud-scoring, detection, and prevention activities or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, to protect our rights and the rights of others, and as otherwise required by law. In addition, DudeComedy may transfer information about you in the event of a business transaction, such as if we or one of our business units or our relevant assets are acquired by, sold to, or merged with another company.

Third Party Links

The Site may contain ads served by reputable third parties, co-promotions or sponsors, as well as links to other web sites or third party applications such as Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn or YouTube. These third parties may view, edit, or set their own cookies. DudeComedy is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these third party ad servers, promoters, web sites or applications, and we advise you to refer to the policy statement of these third parties to understand how they collect and use information.

International Transfer

The Site may be accessible internationally, however our computer systems are currently based in the United States. Therefore, your personally identifiable information will be processed by us in the U.S. where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world, such as the European Union. If you access the Site as a visitor from outside the United States, you consent to the collection and/or processing in the United States of your personally identifiable information, which includes the use of cookies as described above.

GENERAL PROVIONS APPLICABLE TO ALL VISITORS

Sensitive Information

We will not intentionally collect or maintain, and do not want you to provide, any information regarding your medical or health condition, race or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs or other sensitive information.

Children’s Online Privacy Protection

The Site is not designed for or directed to children under the age of 13, and we will not intentionally collect or maintain information about anyone under the age of 13.

Security

The Site has security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of information and data under our control. DudeComedy hosts the Site in a secure server environment that uses a firewall and other advanced technology to prevent interference or access from intruders. These safeguards help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information and data.

Opt-Out Policy

DudeComedy offers its visitors and customers a means to choose how we may use information provided. If, at any time after providing information, you change your mind about receiving information from us or about sharing your information with third parties, send a request specifying your new choice to:contact@dudecomedy.com.

Changes to this Privacy Statement

DudeComedy reserves the right to change this Privacy Statement as reasonably necessary or advisable to accommodate changes to the law, technology or circumstances, and will use reasonable efforts to provide notification of the material changes through the Site at least thirty (30) business days prior to the changes taking effect.

Additional Information

Questions regarding this Statement or the practices of the Site should be directed to DudeComedy’s Security Administrator by e-mailing such questions to: [contact@dudecomedy.com](mailto:contact@dudecomedy.com).

Disputes/Arbitration

DudeComedy will attempt to investigate and promptly resolve any disputes or complaint regarding the interpretation or compliance with this Statement. In the event that DudeComedy is unable to resolve any issues or complaints to your satisfaction, then the dispute, claim or controversy arising out of or relating to this Statement or the breach, termination, enforcement, interpretation or validity thereof, including the determination of the scope or applicability of this Statement to arbitration, shall be determined by arbitration in Seattle, Washington before a single arbitrator.
